<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Betting Strategies</string>
    <string name="title_strategies">Strategies</string>
    <string name="title_favorites">Favorites</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_1">All-in on odds at 1.20 strategy</string>
    <string name="strategy_1">This betting strategy involves winning
        numerous bets one after the other and always using the maximum
        offers the opportunity to earn decent money. But it is also clear
        that all the money is gone if you lose a bet. But if you manage
        to win 30, 35, maybe even 40 times in a row, you’ll get big money!</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_2">The Fibonacci betting system</string>
    <string name="strategy_2">Fibonacci sequence betting is undoubtedly
        a controversial concept. But there are definitely sports bettors
        who were able to achieve great success with it. This strategy
        carries some risks, but with the necessary luck and the right nose,
        you can be successful while employing this strategy.

        The basic concept of betting according to the Fibonacci sequence
        is simple: bet on a tie. If you lose, just bet on the next tie
        according to a certain key and start increasing your stake.</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_3">Dutching in sports betting</string>
    <string name="strategy_3">Dutching is ideal for multi-outcome events
        where you think you can break the possible outcomes down to two or
        three; but in theory, you can bet on any number of selections.
        The fewer selections you make in dutching, the fewer losers you support
        and the more profit you make from them. However, by dutching fewer
        selections, you increase your risk.</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_4">Early cashout in sports betting</string>
    <string name="strategy_4">If the team or player you are supporting is
        in a winning position but is being led out by the opponent,
        then you should definitely make a cashout and secure the appropriate
        profit instead of watching your potential profit and stake vanish
        into thin air. Your forecast proves correct and your choices lose the lead.</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_5">What’s a Money Race?</string>
    <string name="strategy_5">The Money Race can be run with all possible types of bets.
        In most cases, however, the focus is specifically on low odds and thus “safe bets”,
        in order to win as many bets as possible in a row. In this case, the Money
        Race is particularly interesting for sports bettors with a high bankroll.
        If the Money Race is started with a rather high initial stake, you will save
        yourself numerous necessary profits on the way to the self-imposed goal.
        At the same time, however, the risk of loss is also greater.</string>

    <string name="title_strategy_6">Betting on a draw</string>
    <string name="strategy_6">Try to find games where both teams will have
        a hard time defeating each other. For example, look for teams from
        the better league average that compete against top teams at home.
        The visiting team has the quality to not lose, while at the same time
        they will have problems when it comes to actually bending the favourite.
        In this situation, both teams are happy with a draw and that is often the result.</string>
</resources>